question_data = [
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The music group Daft Punk got their name from a negative review they recieved.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The music video to The Buggle&#039;s &quot;Video Killed the Radio Star&quot; was the first music "
                    "video to broadcast on MTV.",
        "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "American rapper Dr. Dre actually has a Ph.D. doctorate.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The song &quot;Stronger Than You&quot; is a single by Estelle, "
                    "who played Garnet in Steven Universe.",
        "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Daft Punk originated in France.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Stevie Wonder&#039;s real name is Stevland Hardaway Morris.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Scatman John&#039;s real name was John Paul Larkin.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Michael Jackson wrote The Simpsons song &quot;Do the Bartman&quot;.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The 2011 movie &quot;The Adventures of Tintin&quot; was directed by Steven Spielberg.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "John Williams composed the music for &quot;Star Wars&quot;.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    }
]
